HiringCat AI QA - Automation Rules
Running: Automation Rules
Using saved authenticated browser session.
Opening automation settings, then creating/toggling/deleting a real QA rule.
REQUEST: API POST /api/automation/rules - {"jobId":"f50f1b76-1f0d-41ce-8bef-2edb0f7f90dd","trigger":"application_submitted","action":"notify_team","conditions":,"actionConfig":}"},"isActive":true,"priority":99}
PASS: API response POST /api/automation/rules - HTTP 200; {"id":"436fb62c-0500-4e93-8e43-8356e83ec076","orgId":"5413bea4-80e3-4d78-b9cd-7933e5db4632","jobId":"f50f1b76-1f0d-41ce-8bef-2edb0f7f90dd","trigger":"application_submitted","conditions":,"action":"notify_team","actionConfig":{"messag
REQUEST: API PATCH /api/automation/rules/436fb62c-0500-4e93-8e43-8356e83ec076/toggle -
PASS: API response PATCH /api/automation/rules/436fb62c-0500-4e93-8e43-8356e83ec076/toggle - HTTP 200;
REQUEST: API GET /api/automation/rules/f50f1b76-1f0d-41ce-8bef-2edb0f7f90dd -
PASS: API response GET /api/automation/rules/f50f1b76-1f0d-41ce-8bef-2edb0f7f90dd - HTTP 200; {"jobRules":[{"id":"436fb62c-0500-4e93-8e43-8356e83ec076","orgId":"5413bea4-80e3-4d78-b9cd-7933e5db4632","jobId":"f50f1b76-1f0d-41ce-8bef-2edb0f7f90dd","trigger":"application_submitted","conditions":,"action":"notify_team","actionCon
REQUEST: API DELETE /api/automation/rules/436fb62c-0500-4e93-8e43-8356e83ec076 -
PASS: API response DELETE /api/automation/rules/436fb62c-0500-4e93-8e43-8356e83ec076 - HTTP 200;
Result: PASS - Automation rule was created, toggled off, listed, and deleted successfully.